

Profile:

Front-end Developer, Audio Engineer, former C-level executive of a multinational talent provider, high school and collegiate-level teacher with a background in web design and e-commerce. Skills include HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, and specializes in React. Additional experience in MySQL, Liquid, Bootstrap, Wordpress, Wix, Photoshop, Illustrator, and more. Prior experience in sales, fundraising, event production, staffing, and customer service. Classically trained musician with strong analysis and memorization skills, and ability to learn new systems quickly. Experienced with DAWs, audio engineering, recording, live sound, lighting, event production, streaming, management, and education K-12 undergrad and post-grad. Fluent in music theory and notation software.

Current Positions:

ANOVA Digital, LLC

Front-end Developer 10/2021 – present

- Works with Shopify and Wordpress to create and maintain user interfaces
- Implements front-end website design revamps
- · Optimizes applications for maximum speed and scalability

Straight Up Digital

Front-end Developer 08/2020 – present

- Develops and maintains user interfaces and implements design on responsive websites
- Builds reusable code and libraries for future use
- Optimizes applications for maximum speed and scalability

Freelance Web Developer

Self-Employed 05/2013 – present www.DanOgrodnik.com

USC Glorya Kaufman School of Dance

Accompanist 05/2016 – present

Previous Experience:

AGBU Vatche and Tamar Manoukian High School

Faculty – Music, Stage Design and Production 05/2017 – 08/2020

Concert Talent

Chief Operating Officer 07/2014 – 01/2017

LA Philharmonic & The Hollywood Bowl

Artist Department 05/2013 – 09/2015

Education:

